<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Castmaker]]></title><description><![CDATA[A static page builder for coming soon pages powered by With Pulp]]></description><link>https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker</link><image><url>https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/logos/logo-512.png</url><title>Castmaker</title><link>https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker</link></image><generator>GatsbyJS Material Starter</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 00:05:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><author><![CDATA[With Pulp]]></author><copyright><![CDATA[Copyright © 2017. With Pulp]]></copyright><item><title><![CDATA[About]]></title><description><![CDATA[Do you have a bunch of domains just lying around and you plan to turn them into ideas later? Well so do we, we have so many that we don't...]]></description><link>https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/about</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/about</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[With Pulp]]></dc:creator><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Do you have a bunch of domains just lying around and you plan to turn them into ideas later? Well so do we, we have so many that we don&apos;t really know which one to start with. So we decided to create a coming soon page builder to quickly put up landing pages to collect data on our domains. This is the idea behind Castmaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an ongoing, open source project that anyone can contribute to, feel free to do what you want with the code. As of right now, we&apos;re going to include some essential components that will make it easy for people to deploy coming soon pages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the project evolves, we&apos;ll write up more information as well as develop more features. Our general goal behind this project is to make it really easy to deploy a coming soon page for products or websites currently in development.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brainstorming Design Ideas]]></title><description><![CDATA[We want to explore. We’re curious people. Look back over history, people have put their lives at stake to go out and explore … We believe in...]]></description><link>https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/brainstorming-design-ideas</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/brainstorming-design-ideas</guid><category><![CDATA[concept]]></category><category><![CDATA[wireframe]]></category><category><![CDATA[sketch]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[With Pulp]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;We want to explore. We’re curious people. Look back over history, people have put their lives at stake to go out and explore … We believe in what we’re doing. Now it’s time to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Astronomy compels the soul to look upward, and leads us from this world to another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who have seen the Earth from space, and for the hundreds and perhaps thousands more who will, the experience most certainly changes your perspective. The things that we share in our world are far more valuable than those which divide us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are all connected; To each other, biologically. To the earth, chemically. To the rest of the universe atomically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dinosaurs are extinct today because they lacked opposable thumbs and the brainpower to build a space program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Science cuts two ways, of course; its products can be used for both good and evil. But there&apos;s no turning back from science. The early warnings about technological dangers also come from science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have an infinite amount to learn both from nature and from each other&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To go places and do things that have never been done before – that’s what living is all about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NASA is not about the ‘Adventure of Human Space Exploration’…We won’t be doing it just to get out there in space – we’ll be doing it because the things we learn out there will be making life better for a lot of people who won’t be able to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are all connected; To each other, biologically. To the earth, chemically. To the rest of the universe atomically.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Setting Up Our Development Environment]]></title><description><![CDATA[We are all connected; To each other, biologically. To the earth, chemically. To the rest of the universe atomically. A Chinese tale tells of...]]></description><link>https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/setting-up-our-development-environment</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/setting-up-our-development-environment</guid><category><![CDATA[webpack]]></category><category><![CDATA[docker]]></category><category><![CDATA[git]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[With Pulp]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;We are all connected; To each other, biologically. To the earth, chemically. To the rest of the universe atomically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Chinese tale tells of some men sent to harm a young girl who, upon seeing her beauty, become her protectors rather than her violators. That&apos;s how I felt seeing the Earth for the first time. I could not help but love and cherish her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you could see the earth illuminated when you were in a place as dark as night, it would look to you more splendid than the moon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here men from the planet Earth first set foot upon the Moon. July 1969 AD. We came in peace for all mankind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The regret on our side is, they used to say years ago, we are reading about you in science class. Now they say, we are reading about you in history class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want to explore. We’re curious people. Look back over history, people have put their lives at stake to go out and explore … We believe in what we’re doing. Now it’s time to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don&apos;t intend to waste any of mine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never in all their history have men been able truly to conceive of the world as one: a single sphere, a globe, having the qualities of a globe, a round earth in which all the directions eventually meet, in which there is no center because every point, or none, is center — an equal earth which all men occupy as equals. The airman&apos;s earth, if free men make it, will be truly round: a globe in practice, not in theory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Failure is not an option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Problems look mighty small from 150 miles up.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Choosing The Right Stack]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Earth was small, light blue, and so touchingly alone, our home that must be defended like a holy relic. The Earth was absolutely round...]]></description><link>https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/choosing-the-right-stack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://withpulp.github.io/castmaker/choosing-the-right-stack</guid><category><![CDATA[node]]></category><category><![CDATA[mongo]]></category><category><![CDATA[react]]></category><category><![CDATA[express]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[With Pulp]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;The Earth was small, light blue, and so touchingly alone, our home that must be defended like a holy relic. The Earth was absolutely round. I believe I never knew what the word round meant until I saw Earth from space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It suddenly struck me that that tiny pea, pretty and blue, was the Earth. I put up my thumb and shut one eye, and my thumb blotted out the planet Earth. I didn&apos;t feel like a giant. I felt very, very small.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we got further and further away, it [the Earth] diminished in size. Finally it shrank to the size of a marble, the most beautiful you can imagine. That beautiful, warm, living object looked so fragile, so delicate, that if you touched it with a finger it would crumble and fall apart. Seeing this has to change a man.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many say exploration is part of our destiny, but it’s actually our duty to future generations and their quest to ensure the survival of the human species.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never in all their history have men been able truly to conceive of the world as one: a single sphere, a globe, having the qualities of a globe, a round earth in which all the directions eventually meet, in which there is no center because every point, or none, is center — an equal earth which all men occupy as equals. The airman&apos;s earth, if free men make it, will be truly round: a globe in practice, not in theory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Failure is not an option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Science has not yet mastered prophecy. We predict too much for the next year and yet far too little for the next 10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want to explore. We’re curious people. Look back over history, people have put their lives at stake to go out and explore … We believe in what we’re doing. Now it’s time to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What was most significant about the lunar voyage was not that man set foot on the Moon but that they set eye on the earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have an infinite amount to learn both from nature and from each other&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>